{
    "subject": "resource/Arch_of_Hadrian_(Athens)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Landmarks_in_Athens",
    "human_readable": "The Arch of Hadrian in Athens is about Landmarks in Athens.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9859484434127808,
            "question": "Is the Arch of Hadrian a famous landmark in Athens?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8166872262954712,
            "question": "Are there any other significant historical structures in Athens besides the Arch of Hadrian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7540106177330017,
            "question": "Why is the Arch of Hadrian important to Athenian history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6967831254005432,
            "question": "Where is the Arch of Hadrian located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6557565331459045,
            "question": "What can you tell me about landmarks in Athens?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.616065263748169,
            "question": "Who built the Arch of Hadrian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5929601788520813,
            "question": "Can you describe the architectural style of the Arch of Hadrian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5832754969596863,
            "question": "What type of structure is the Arch of Hadrian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5054737329483032,
            "question": "When was the Arch of Hadrian built?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4988853931427002,
            "question": "What is the purpose or history behind the Arch of Hadrian?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Arch of Hadrian in Athens is about Landmarks in Athens.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4575_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the Arch of Hadrian built?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4575_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of structure is the Arch of Hadrian?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4575_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the architectural style of the Arch of Hadrian?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4575_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4575_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4575_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4575_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4575_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4575_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4575_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4575_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4575_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4575_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4575_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's my evaluation:\n\n* Document content mentions \"triumphal monument\", \"symbol of Roman power and influence\", \"historical landmark\", \"architectural grandeur\", and \"must-see landmarks\" which suggests that the Arch of Hadrian is indeed about Landmarks in Athens.\n* The documents also provide details about the historical significance, construction, and features of the Arch of Hadrian, further supporting its relevance to Landmarks in Athens.\n\nTherefore, my answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that the Arch of Hadrian is a historical landmark and tourist hotspot in Athens, which supports the statement that it is about landmarks in Athens."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}